Scouts already checked it.
暗探仔细查过了
All the people from Nonuple Palace
九重幽宫的人
had left.
的确都走了
It's said Jing Yuan
听说是被井渊
used Nonuple Token
发布九幽令
to call them back.
强行召回的
It seems that
看来啊
we can
我们最近
catch our breath for a while.
可以稍做歇息了
No.
不
Somehow, I think
我反而觉得
he may smell something.
他似乎是察觉了什么
What?
什么
I was with Jin Baiwan
这一路上
all the way.
我都与金百万同行
If Nonuple Palace's people
若是被九重幽宫的人
found some points,
发现出了端倪
it wouldn't be surprising.
倒也不奇怪
Fortunately,
所幸
I know
我也终于弄清
who she was.
她的身份了
Right.
也是
No one would know
谁会知道这么巧
Miss Jin
金姑娘居然
was from Nonuple Palace.
是九重幽宫的人
Baiwan lost her memory now,
如今百万失忆
so I can't let her
我就更不能让她
be in Jing Yuan's hands.
落入井渊手中
So,
那
what's the next step?
咱们接下来怎么办
Hold a wedding ceremony.
成婚
As long as Baiwan gets married with me,
只要百万与我成婚
she will officially become
正式有了
Mrs. Qu of Tingqin Garden.
听琴苑苑主夫人的称号
Even Nonuple Palace
就是九重幽宫
can't do anything bad to her.
也奈何不了她
Getting married with her?
真成婚哪
Are you serious?
这么急
Will she agree on that?
她能同意吗
You go ask Mr Wang
你就让王管家
to have all the wedding things
先把婚礼要准备的事情
well prepared.
都准备好
When the time is right,
等时机成熟了
I'll tell her.
我自然会通知她
Okay.
好
By the way,
不过啊
I disclosed your birthday
我那天一不小心
to her accidentally.
透露了阿徵你的生辰
Accidentally?
不小心
So,
所以嘛
I guess Miss Jin
金姑娘
may be busy with
估计现在肯定在忙着
your birthday gifts now.
给你准备生辰礼物呢
You're welcome.
可不要太感谢我呦
Well,
如此
that's all right.
倒也挺好
Birthday?
生辰
Close your mouth,
你别张嘴
or you'll get wrinkles.
小心有皱纹
Birthday?
生辰
Zheng didn't want to tell me his birthday.
阿徵都不愿告诉我
If Song Jianshan didn't let it slip,
要不是宋涧山说漏嘴了
I wouldn't know it.
我都不知道
Does it work?
你这玩意儿能有用吗
That's the face cream
这可是灼灼家
with Zhuozhuo's secret-recipe.
秘制的美容膏
It can make you
美容养颜
not age a day.
青春永驻
Nice.
说得好
Baiwan
那这么说
You plan to
百万这次是打算
hold a wonderful birthday party for Lord Qu,
好好帮曲苑主
right?
办一次生辰了
He offended so many people
他因为我
because of me.
得罪了那么多人
He can't invite more guests anymore,
也没办法再宴请宾客了
but
不过
I have an idea.
我有个主意
I tell you...
我告诉你们
That's amazing!
那这么说也太棒了
What do you think of it?
你觉得呢
You've done a lot for his birthday.
你这么用心
It's worth that I voluntarily
也不枉我把曲苑主
give him up to you.
让给你吧
You give him to me?
什么叫你让给我呀
Yes, of course?
你以为不是我让给你
You...
你能
We three
大家都是
are best sisters.
相亲相爱的好姐妹
We shouldn't argue for a man.
不要因为一个男人
It's not worth it.
在这里
Sisters? No way.
谁跟她是好姐妹了
Zheng
阿徵
The wedding dresses are prepared.
喜服都准备好了
You can go have a check if you have a minute.
有时间你就去看看
Okay.
好
Be careful with that.
但是千万注意啊
Make sure Baiwan can't know anything.
不要被百万给发现了
You can count on me.
我办事你还不放心啊
What are you talking about?
你们在聊什么呢
Nothing.
没什么
Zheng is teaching me
我 我让阿徵
how to write well.
帮我看看字
Writing?
看个练字
But why do you look suspicious?
怎么鬼鬼祟祟的
Baiwan
百万
What brings you here?
你找我什么事啊
I heard all the people outside had gone away.
我听说外面的人都走了
There will be a temple fair tomorrow night.
明天晚上街道会有庙会
So you want to go out, Baiwan?
百万是想出去
Can I?
可以吗
Of course, if you like.
只要百万想 自然可以
Really?
真的
Then we have a deal.
那我们约好了
We'll enjoy it tomorrow night.
明天晚上去看庙会
Deal.
好
Sorry, sir.
这位客官
It's closing time.
小店马上就要打烊了
Come back tomorrow, please.
还请明日再来吧
Closing time?
打烊
Mercy, please.
这位好汉
Take whatever you want.
你要什么随便拿
The cash...
钱
Cash is on the counter.
钱在柜台
Young Host of Palace
少宫主
I have checked this out.
我已经调查过了
This food shop is the biggest one
这儿是整个青衣镇
in Qingyi Town.
最大的粮店
Well, sort of.
算是 算是
Tingqin Garden
听琴苑
is an influential family there.
是这个镇上的名门
And they usually purchase food there,
粮食采买
right?
应该都在这儿吧
Yeah.
是 是
A butler of Tingqin Garden
听琴苑每五天
purchases food and basic goods
就会有个管家出门
every five days.
专门采购一些吃穿用度
He actually purchases food
米面粮油
from here.
确实是小店负责
When will he come here
那下次
next time?
他们什么时候过来
He...
他们
Today.
今天
He will disguise himself as an antique shop owner, named Wang.
他会化名古董店王老板
Mr Xu
徐老板
Our shopkeeper went out to visit relatives.
掌柜出门探亲了
Just ask me if you have any needs.
您有事吩咐我就行
I'm the owner of antique shop, Wang.
我是古董店的王老板
The shopkeeper must tell you I would be here, right?
掌柜的跟你吩咐过了吧
Yes, sir. He told me about it.
是 吩咐过了
The usual, sir?
一切照旧是吗
Yeah, but 30 percent more food and oil than before.
粮油再多三成
You also sell
你们这儿还卖一些
red dates, longans,
红枣 桂圆
lotus seeds and something like that, right?
莲子什么的是吧
Yes, sir.
是 是
I'll have five kilograms each.
每样都来十斤
-Okay. -By the way.
好 还有啊
Who is the best jewelry artisan
这镇上最厉害的珠宝匠
in this town?
是哪一家
Well, you need peanuts, red dates,
这又是花生红枣
and jewelry,
又是珠宝的
does your family have a happy event?
府上可是有喜事啊
It's just a normal wedding,
寻常人家的婚事
nothing special.
没什么特别的
I got to go
那我就先走了啊
and take all the staffs later.
等一会儿过来拿
Who'll get married?
谁的婚事
It must be Chu, right?
阿初要结婚
I don't know any Chu.
我不认识什么阿初
Tell me,
我问你
will Chu
阿初是不是要跟
get married with Qu Zheng from Tingqin Garden?
听琴苑的曲徵结婚
It seems that
尊驾这副模样
you want to do something bad to Tingqin Garden.
是要对听琴苑不利啊
I won't tell you a word.
我不便多说
Bring me to Tingqin Garden,
带我进听琴苑
or I'll kill you.
不然我杀了你
Each one from Tingqin Garden
我们听琴苑的人
is not a coward.
绝不会贪生怕死
Young Host of Palace
少宫主
So...
这下
Wedding...
婚事
Amazing!
好
Cool! Another show!
好 再来一个 再来一个
Thank you.
多谢
That's so cool!
好 好 好
How are the preparations going?
你们准备怎么样了
I'm Su Zhuozhuo.
我苏灼灼办事
You can count on me.
你还不放心
It's the last thing he'll expect.
他绝对想不到
He's not gonna expect
绝对想不到
you can have such a big surprise
你会给他准备
for him.
这么大一个惊喜
Keep your voice down, Baiwan.
百万 小点声
Don't you want to visit temple fair?
你不是要去逛庙会吗
The fair is there.
庙会在那边
I'm not here
我今天过来
for the temple fair.
不是去庙会的
Then what's it about?
那是为了什么
Well...
其实
I have a surprise for you.
我给你准备了个惊喜
A surprise?
惊喜
What is it?
什么惊喜
Close your eyes, and turn around.
你把眼睛闭上 转过去
I'll take you to there.
我带你去看
What are you doing?
你俩这是干啥呢
It's none of your business.
关你什么事
Let's go.
走走走
We're friends.
都是好朋友
Why don't you tell me about it?
告诉我一下嘛
Go report to Young Host of Palace.
快去通知少宫主
We found Jin Baiwan.
发现金百万
Yes, sir.
是
Young Master of Valley
少谷主
We buy the novels
我们这每天来买
written by Young Mrs. every day.
少夫人的话本
Does it work?
这管用吗
Qiuer is trapped in Tingqin Garden.
秋儿现在被困在听琴苑
The novel is the only way
她唯一可以传播消息的
that she can deliver messages.
便是这话本了
There must be some secrets
这话本里
in these novels.
一定有什么玄机
Excuse me.
老板
Is there the Barefaced...
请问有厚颜无耻
I mean by Qiu Qiuer?
秋秋儿的最新话本吗
You mean Barefaced Yu Lingfeng, right?
厚颜无耻玉零风吧
There it is.
有有有
I'll get it for you.
我这就给您拿去
Thank you.
有劳了
That's weird.
这么多歪道
I think
我看你
you just love reading novels.
分明就是爱上了看话本
Nonsense.
胡说
How could I love reading that vul...
我怎么会喜欢看这些低
Vul...
低
Look at you.
你看 你看 你看
You don't even use the word "vulgar"now.
你现在都不说它低俗了
Well, I can't say it's vulgar.
低俗我感觉倒不至于
And it's easy to read,
而且它
appealing to all social groups.
文字通畅 雅俗共赏
Qiuer
秋儿
Young Master of Valley
少谷主
Young Mrs can't be there.
哪儿有少夫人啊
It's impossible.
不可能
It must be Qiuer.
绝对是秋儿
Go find her.
快去找
Zheng
阿徵
Open your eyes.
睁开眼睛吧
I know
我知道
today is your birthday,
今天是你的生辰
so I
所以
have a surprise for you.
为你准备了惊喜
It's the first time I've celebrated the birthday for you.
因为之前的二十四年
I missed those 24 birthdays before.
都没有能陪你一起
So tonight,
所以今天
I'll make it up.
我要把这些都补上
That's the gift
这是我送你的
for your one-year-old birthday.
一岁生日礼物
Though a lot of things
虽然那天
had happened in the world
江湖上应该
on that day,
发生了很多事情
the most important thing for me
但是于我而言
was your birth.
最重要的是你的出生
Because...
因为
You're a beam of light of my life.
你是我生命的一束光
I should've said that
这句话
to you.
应该是我说才是
Well, let me finish.
你让我说完嘛
That's for your two-year-old birthday.
这是你两岁的生日礼物
It's sweet.
很甜
Kids love candies.
小孩子都爱吃糖
But you can't eat too much,
但是不能多吃
or it'll rot your teeth out.
吃多了老了会掉牙
Then
这样
you couldn't eat meals cooked by me.
你就没法吃我做的饭了
I must have the meals made by you
百万做的饭
forever.
我自然要吃一辈子
When you were three years old,
三岁的时候
you must know how to write.
你应该会写字了吧
All these Ink brushes are for you.
这些毛笔都是给你的
So you can record
以后就能记录下
all the moments with me.
每天跟我发生的事情
When you were four years old,
四岁的时候
you must begin to learn how to use a sword.
应该学会练剑了
Because you would travel all over the world
因为二十一年后的你
with me 21 years later,
要跟我一起
taking a sword.
仗剑行走天涯
You didn't expect
你是不是从来也没想过
you could meet me, right?
会遇到我
Before that,
之前
it's you who take care of me,
一直是你在照顾我
and keep me safe.
保护我
And I want to do the same to you,
我也想像你一样
taking care of you
照顾你
and keeping you safe.
保护你
I'll give you everything best.
把最好的一切都给你
If you can always
百万只要能
be with me,
一直陪在我身边
it'll be everything
对我来说
for me.
便是最好的
I will.
我当然会一直陪着你了
Let's see other gifts for you.
我们再看看别的礼物吧
Okay.
好
Oh no.
完了
Why there are only
怎么只有
24 gifts?
二十四个礼物了
I left
我把最重要的
the most important one.
那个给忘了
You have prepared so many gifts for me.
百万给我准备了那么多
That's enough.
已经足够了
No.
那不行
That's the most important one.
那可是最重要的一个
Stay here. I'll take it for you.
你等我给你拿回来啊
Baiwan
百万
The streets are not safe.
而今外面并不太平
Let me
要不
go with you?
我还是陪你一同去吧
No.
不用
It's over there. It's close.
就在前面 很近的
That's a surprise for you,
这是你的生日惊喜
so I won't let you know what it is.
当然不能让你知道了
I'll be right back.
我很快就回来
Okay.
好
I'll be there.
我等你啊
Why did I never meet someone
我怎么就没遇见
like him?
这么一个人呢
Was you afraid of seeing
你刚才是不是怕
them showing PDA?
看见别人甜甜蜜蜜的
But you're alone,
自己却孤苦伶仃一个人
so you left there, right?
所以才先走的
I make up my mind
本姑娘独身
to be a single lady.
是自己的选择
Nobody needs you,
你这种没人要的呀
so you're a real bachelor.
才叫孤苦伶仃
Nobody needs me?
我没人要
If I'm not afraid a relationship
我要不是怕谈情说爱
can influence my adventure,
影响我行走江湖
numerous matchmakers
那听琴苑的门槛
will come to Tingqin Garden.
都得被说媒的踩平了
You know?
你信不信
Crap!
我呸
Well,
我看啊
you want to get some shots today.
你今天就是找扎
Wait and see
咱俩今天不一定
who will get shots among us.
谁扎谁
You're good, huh?
挺厉害呀
Yeah?
怎么着
Well...
那个
I'm stuck by a plot
我新话本里
in my new novel.
有一个情节卡住了
Help me figure out how to write it.
你帮我想想吧
You mean
你是说
the unfinished chapter of
纯情镖师俏劫匪
Innocent Escort And Pretty Robber.
未出的那一章
I think
我觉得呀
it should end with
那个大结局就应该改成
flower rain.
天空中下满花瓣雨
How romantic it is!
多浪漫呀
Flower rain?
花瓣雨
That's old school!
这都多少年前的情节了
So corny.
你太土了吧
You know sh*t.
你懂个屁
Flower rain is so beautiful.
花瓣雨才唯美呢
Muqiu
金小姐
I have an idea.
你听我的
At the end,
最后就让两个人
the two people can climb into
一起登上一个
a huge sky lantern,
巨大的孔明灯
overlooking a flower field
飞到半空中
covered the ground
俯瞰铺满整片
when they're flying to the sky.
大地的花田
How about that?
怎么样
Qiuqiu
秋秋
Just make a choice.
选一个
Right.
是啊
Muqiu
金小姐
Just make your choice.
选一个吧
I... I will think about it both.
我 我都会参考的
Well...
那个
I...
我
You must be thirsty.
大家一定都口渴了吧
Let's have some drink. I'm buying.
我请大家喝糖水
You are not worth
我跟你说话
my breath or time.
就白费口舌我
Excuse me.
店家
One bowl of sugar cane juice.
给我来碗甘蔗汁
I'll have one, too.
老板 我也来碗
Sorry.
抱歉啊
There is one left.
只剩一碗甘蔗汁了
Qiuqiu
秋秋
Give us a minute.
避一避
Okay. I'll leave.
好好好 我这就走
Qi?
阿七
What are you doing?
你干嘛
I want to take you someplace.
我带你去个地方
Keep my hands off!
你放手
My husband is waiting for me.
我夫君还在等我呢
What husband?
什么夫君
Don't let Qu Zheng fool you.
你不要再被曲徵
He is a liar.
那个小人蒙蔽了
I'm the one
我才是那个
you can trust.
你可以相信的人
Leave me alone!
你放手
Let's go.
走
What're you doing?
你干什么
Why did you have to fight me for the juice?
一碗甘蔗汁你也抢
Nobody got that,
最后谁都没喝到
and we paid for a broken bowl.
还赔了一个碗
I drank it.
谁说我没喝到
I got the last sip.
碗底那口就让我喝到了
I...
我
It's so sweet.
真甜
Where's Baiwan?
百万呢
Lord
苑主
Something happened to your wife.
夫人出事了
What?
什么
She was taken away
夫人被九重幽宫的人
by the people from Nonuple Palace.
掳走了
What?
什么
Let's split up.
分头去找
Okay.
是
What're you doing?
干嘛呀
Go get Baiwan!
赶紧去找百万哪
No.
不
You have to take the news to Tingqin Garden,
你赶紧回听琴苑报信
and bring more people here.
带更多人马来
Let's split up.
我们分头去找 走
Let's go.
走
Darling
相公
That's funny.
这个真好玩
I'm glad to hear that.
你喜欢就好
I like it.
当然喜欢了
Qiuer
秋儿
Brother Shu
阿树哥哥
Great!
太好了
Qu Zheng let you go finally.
那个曲徵把你放出来了
He did not give you a hard time, did he?
他没有为难你吧
I thought you left.
你没走啊
How could I?
我怎么会走呢
Come on.
来
I'm gonna take you out of here.
我带你离开这儿
I'm a guest of Tingqin Garden.
我去听琴苑是去做客的
Baiwan and Lord Qu
百万和曲苑主
promised me they would go easy on me.
答应不会为难我
You still speak for Qu Zheng now,
你到现在
don't you?
还在帮那个曲徵说话
He kidnapped you.
你被他掳走了
You have no idea
岳父大人有多着急
how worried your father is.
你知道吗
Actually, Baiwan missed me...
其实是百万想我了
I'll explain it
这件事我自然
to my Dad.
会跟爹解释
I have to go to Baiwan now.
我先去找百万了
You.
你
Qiuer
秋儿
At this point...
这事到如今了
If you're mad at me,
你心里就算有气
you need to get over it.
也该消了
Right.
对啊
It was you who made a such a big trouble
明明就是你自己
in Taoyuan Valley.
在桃源谷闯的大娄子
We've found you, finally.
现在好不容易见面了
Don't you want to escape from us?
你难道还想开溜不成
-You -Jueming
你 决明
Wait.
等等
This is Baiwan's stuff.
这不是百万的东西吗
Why is it here?
怎么会在这儿
What're you doing here?
你们怎么在这儿啊
Qiuqiu
秋秋
Something happened to Baiwan.
百万出事了
What?
什么
I will say it again.
我再说一遍
Stop.
停车
You still want to go back to him?
你还想回去找他
He's my husband.
他是我夫君
You heard me?
我自然要找他
I did that for your own good.
我这都是为了你好
Why do you have to
你为什么还要
continue to
这么执迷不悟
trust Qu Zheng, a creep?
去相信曲徵这种小人
I don't see any good that you kidnapped me on the street.
当街抢人这叫为我好
And you called Zheng a creep.
还说阿徵是小人
Aren't you shifting the blame?
这难道不是倒打一耙吗
From what I've seen,
我看你们分明
you just want to use me
就是想利用我
against Zheng.
对付阿徵罢了
Leave me alone.
让开
I never lied to you.
我从来没有骗过你
Do you expect me to believe what you said,
你觉得我会相信你们
instead of his words?
不信他吗
What if I told you
可如果我告诉你
everything was a trap
从你送经之路一开始
set by Qu Zheng
所有的一切
when you began to escort the sacred book.
都是曲徵设下的圈套呢
Qu Zheng is the one
曲徵才是这一切的
that is behind this.
幕后黑手
It was him who hired you
也是那本假的璞元真经
to escort the fake Puyuan Canon.
真正的托镖人
I won't
我不会信你们
fall your crap.
这种鬼话的
About the Bloody Moon tattoo on your hand...
你手上的血月标记
Only the high priests in Nonuple Palace
只有九重幽宫的
can keep that.
男女大祭司才有
The male priest is called Envoy Heiyun.
男为黑云使
The female priest is called Envoy Xueyue.
女为雪月使
Everyone knows about it.
此事江湖皆知
Okay.
好
Even if I was from
就算我真是
Nonuple Palace,
九重幽宫的人
it wouldn't have anything to do
那这跟你刚刚说的事情
with your words.
没有任何关系
Five years ago,
五年前
you were ordered to destroy Xu's family,
你奉命去追讨屠杀徐家
stealing the sacred book.
盗走经书的罪魁祸首
After that, you disappeared, lost your memories.
从此失踪 失忆
Then Qu Zheng pretended to be close to you,
此后曲徵就接近你
and fool you.
蒙骗你
Think about why?
你觉得是为什么
What are you trying to say?
你到底什么意思
All of these
这所有的一切
is because he wanted to get
他都是为了得到那本
the real Puyuan Canon.
真正的璞元真经
A person can prove my words.
有一个人
You'll know I don't lie to you
如果你见到她
if you meet her.
就知道我没有在骗你
You mean Baiwan
你说百万
was taken away by Young Host of Palace?
被那个少宫主带走了
I have to
我现在得
take the news to Tingqin Garden.
赶去听琴苑报信
Mr Yu
御公子
Since you're here,
既然你在
can you take care of Qiuqiu for me
麻烦你照顾好秋秋
and find Baiwan with her?
陪她一起去寻寻百万吧
Qiuer
秋儿
Don't worry, Qiuer.
秋儿 你莫急
Nonuple Palace
这九重幽宫
is a decent school.
也是名门正派
They said
他们既然号称
Baiwan was a disciple
这百万姑娘
of the palace,
是他们宫中的弟子
so I think
想必
they wouldn't give a hard time to her.
也一定不会为难她的
Right.
对对对
Then Miss Jin
正好金小姐
can go back her school.
就回师门了嘛
What are you talking about?
什么师门
Have you ever seen a decent school
你们见过哪个名门正派
kidnap a woman many times?
几次三番掳走一个女子
For me,
我看是土匪强盗
they're bandits!
还差不多
We just don't know the facts.
如今这事实不清
No one can settle
听琴苑和九重幽宫
the dispute
之间的是非
between Nonuple Palace and Tingqin Garden.
谁也不能妄下定论
That's not a dispute.
什么是非恩怨我没见过
They kidnapped Baiwan.
他们强行带走百万
I can't drop her.
这事我不能不管
I never said we could sit on our hands.
我没说不管百万姑娘
Well, Qiuer.
这样 秋儿
You go back to Taoyuan Valley with me first.
你跟我先回桃源谷
I'll send people to find her
等回去之后
when we arrive there.
我再派人去找她
It'll be too late
等你回到桃源谷
when you go back to Taoyuan Valley.
什么都来不及了
No one knows
百万到时候
what will happen to Baiwan.
都不知道怎么样了
I'll find her myself
你要是不愿意帮我找
if you don't want to help me!
我就自己去找
Qiuer
秋儿
Lord
苑主
It's now known
已经查明
Mrs Qu was taken away to a wagon
夫人被九重幽宫的
by the Young Host of Nonuple Palace.
少宫主劫上了马车
According to the tracks,
按车辙看
they headed to
他们似乎是往
Wanlan Town.
万澜镇方向去了
Go inform all the disciples
通知所有弟子
to Wanlan Town.
一起向万澜镇集结
Yes, Lord.
是
Have you got Baiwan?
找到百万了吗
We knew they went to Wanlan Town.
已经追踪到了万澜镇
Zheng has been on the way there.
阿徵先行一步
I'll take the disciples to help him.
我带着弟子们赶去支援
Wanlan Town?
万澜镇
I'm coming with you.
那我跟你一起去
Let's go.
走
Young Master of Valley
少谷主
We're not going there, are we?
咱们就不去万澜镇了吧
The most important thing
秋儿妹妹现在
for Qiuer
心头要紧之事
is to get Baiwan back.
便是找回金百万姑娘
I have to help her
我必须要帮她
solve it,
解决这件事
or
不然
she won't go back to Taoyuan Valley.
她绝不肯回到桃源谷的
Yes, master.
是
Let's go.
走
Where are we?
这是哪儿啊
You'll see.
你进去就知道了
Mrs Lord
苑主夫人
You're...
你是那个
Xiaocui
小翠
It was Lord and Mrs Lord that
是夫人和苑主
let Qingyun
让擎云大哥
send me here, right?
送我来这儿的吧
I planned to go to Tingqin Garden
我原本是想去听琴苑
to repay Lord Qu
报答曲苑主的
for saving my life.
救命之恩的
Anyway,
不过
I'll do anything
只要是苑主的安排
the Lord asks.
小翠都听的
You were saying
你说
Zheng saved your life,
阿徵是你的救命恩人
so you went to Tingqin Garden
所以你千里迢迢
after a long journey?
到了听琴苑
Yes.
没错
Without Lord Qu,
要不是曲苑主
I would
我恐怕早就被那个
have been killed by
杀千刀的刑老六
the damned Xing Laoliu.
给活活打死了
Xing Laoliu
刑老六
Trust me.
您放心
All the goods escorted by our agency
咱们镖局东西
are stored in special boxes.
都是用特制密盒保存的
No one can open it except the escort.
除非押镖人谁都打不开
I'll deliver it to Yinxue Village.
我一定安全送达隐雪村
That's good.
那就好
I'll leave the sacred book
这本经书啊
to you then.
就拜托镖师了
You mean
你说的是
the man
那个住在靖边镇
with a dark mole around his mouth,
嘴边长了个黑痣的
who lived in Jinbian Town?
刑老六
Right.
没错
How did you know him?
你怎么会认识他的
I
我
Since you're the wife of Lord,
既然你是苑主夫人
I'll tell you the truth.
小翠就不瞒你了
I bought you back.
爷把你们买回来
This is not a place for free meals!
是让你们吃干饭的吗
If you're not serious about
不好好学唱歌跳舞
dancing and singing,
怎么高价把你们
how can I sell you to brothel
卖到青楼啊
Master
老爷
Your important guest is coming.
贵客到
Just stay here!
都老老实实给我待着
Sir
公子
Puyuan Canon?
璞元真经
Just send it
你只管把这个
to Jin's Escort Agency.
送到金氏镖局
Ask them to deliver it
让他们送给一个
to a man named Qing Songke.
叫青松客的人
And I'll
报酬
pay for that.
自然少不了你的
A few days later,
但没两天
that young man
这位公子
arrested Xing Laoliu,
就把刑老六抓了
helping us get out there.
救了我们出去
You mean Qu Zheng gave Puyuan Canon
你说是曲徵把璞元真经
to Xing Laoliu,
交给了刑老六
And had him to hire Jin's Escort Agency?
让他找金氏镖局运送的
Right.
对
Puyuan Canon
璞元真经
I think that's the name of the book.
好像就是这么个名字
No way.
不可能
You must have made a mistake.
你一定认错人了
I didn't know
我原先啊
who the young man was before.
也不知道那位公子是谁
Later,
后来
I had been to Taoyuan Valley accidentally.
机缘巧合去了桃源谷
I found
我才发现
that man
原来那位公子啊
was a big shot,
就是鼎鼎大名的
the Lord of Tingqin Garden.
听琴苑曲苑主
It was impossible that I made a mistake.
我不可能认错的
No.
不可能
I don't believe it.
我不信
He wouldn't lie to me.
阿徵不可能骗我的
You got Xiaocui
这个小翠
to set Zheng up, right?
是你找来诬陷阿徵的吧
You'll see
她说的是真是假
if you go have a check in Jinbian Town.
你去靖边镇一查便知
Why
为什么你到现在
don't you believe
还不相信
Qu Zheng is the man
曲徵就是这一切的
who behind this?
谋划人
Okay.
好
In that case,
既然如此
I want to hear it from him.
我要阿徵亲口告诉我
Do you think
你觉得
I can let you
我还会放你
go back to him?
回到他身边吗
Leave her alone!
放开她
I said,
我说了
Who do you think you are?
你以为你自己算什么
You don't get to talk to me
你有什么资格
like that.
说这样的话
Are you fine?
没事吧
I want you to tell me
我要你告诉我
if you are the one
璞元真经真正的托镖人
who asked me to deliver the sacred book.
是不是你
So,
所以
you set up the whole thing,
这一切都是你设的局
right?
是吗
So,
所以
you've been lying to me,
你一直都在骗我
right?
对不对
Baiwan
百万
I can explain it to you
等我们回到听琴苑
after going back to Tingqin Garden.
我再好好跟你解释
Keep my hands off!
你放手
Since you're the man
你既然就是那个
behind this,
罪魁祸首
there's nothing to explain.
你还有什么好解释的
Baiwan
百万
Leave me alone.
别碰我
I don't want to see your face again.
我再也不想看见你
Go!
你走
You can blame me
你怪我也好
or hate me.
怨我也好
All I want is to keep you safe.
我只要你平安